I have to start somewhere and I am lost
stuck on being able to explain this idea
this concept I think can save our planet
and humanity but it's complex and I want
to be able to do it in five minutes and
explain it and that's just not possible
so where I'm at is there and I just need
to start explaining it so I'm going to
keep explaining it in five minute videos
until I figure it out so join my channel
subscribe to my channel join me in the
journey towards saving the world today's
video is the attempting to explain it I
think there is a lot of power in
ownership and in capitalism where the 1%
own half the wealth that's ridiculous
that's not capitalism it's not designed
to be efficient it's not designed to be
sustainable and I mean it has pieces of
it it is designed to be monetarily
sustainable and efficient that the money
you make but it's not designed for the
resources to be sustainable so it's a
little more about the problem which I
don't really want to talk about
ownership in communism is everything is
owned by the government which
theoretically is working for the people
so if we said that it's owned by the
people but really it's not it's central
planning and there's still the people in
power who have control over everything
and there's beautiful things of
communism but I don't think that's one
of them I think that we can create a
world where we the people everyone not
the 99% not the 1% a hundred percent of
people own what we've created together
and we don't take it by force we don't
take it but we just create it together
through collaboration and cooperation
and being able to collaborate on
projects and figure out the problems and
not just leave it up to our governments
to decide on how we're gonna solve the
climate crisis and how we're gonna not
go to war constantly we the people have
those discussions and yes we don't have
power at the moment and that is for one
person and ten people and a hundred
people different things open up to us
the one were a million people a billion
people six billion people we change the
world that way and there's so much
possibility and so many ideas I have
here but it can't be explained in a five
minute video but we're able to share
knowledge and resources we share power
and when people unite there's nothing
they can't do and I think we have more
in common than we have that separates us
and there are things that separate us
and we're gonna have to figure that
stuff out to live peacefully and allow
people to be individuals and not be
dictated by the mass to do things that
aren't um unless they're unethical that
they hurt other people the environment
idea but that's it that we we create
everything together and own it all
together and especially in the beginning
I totally get that it's not everyone's
cup of tea I'm looking for the people
this excites them or they can see this
vision of the future a world with zero
poverty where everyone's able to live
their best life because they're not
worried about the stress of putting food
on the table and a roof over their head
that we're able to solve those problems
together and it's not gonna be solved
overnight but we have to look at where
we are and where we're gonna be the path
to get there and that means figuring out
how to feed yourself and your family and
your community in your neighborhood and
then be able to share that information
being able to learn permaculture
together learn how to do vertical bar
being different solutions are gonna work
for different people and different
places on this planet that aren't gonna
work for every where and that's where I
think communism is too uniform and the
central ownership leads to corruption
where when we own it all together and
you can be part of every everything that
means something to you can be part of
that discussion as much a part of that
discussion as you want you can trust the
mass and just kind of step back and
allow other people to to make the
decisions or you can be your voice and
or give your vote to someone else and
there's it's complex the idea I have is
both simple cuz the idea of that we all
own everything that we create not just
everything we don't just own everything
one day but as we create it we add it to
this global cooperative there's just so
much beauty and potential there and this
video is now five minutes in 30 seconds
so I'm gonna stop it here and then maybe
not tomorrow cuz it's the weekend but
it's on Monday I will be posting another
video that explains another piece of it
and hopefully the right people and
hopefully the right people will watch it
when I explain it in the right way at
the right time the right people will
come and it's hard to trust an app when
I have
this idea for when I see the solution to
all of the most of that let's not say
all of them most of the misery and
inequality and it's hard to have the
solution and not be able to just poof
make it happen but this is me making it
happen from where I am and what I'm
capable of doing right now which isn't
even edited editing a video it's just
posting it as it is that's what I'll do
and I'll keep on keep it on thanks